Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Administrative Files, 1982-2017; 23.5 Linear Feet in 37 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 2.39 Gigabytes in 1,807 files
  - Grant Files -- Democracy Alliance, 2008; cuid39572 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_266)
  - Grant Files -- Wallace Global Fund, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Grant Files -- Instructional Television Foundation, 2008-2009; cuid39575 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_271)
  - Grant Files -- New York University Humanities Council, 2008-2009; cuid39576 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_276)
  - Grant Files -- Caipirinha Foundation, 2008-2010; cuid39571 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_262)
  - Grant Files -- Experimental Television Center, 2008-2010; cuid39573 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_267)
  - Grant Files -- NY Department of Cultural Affairs, Cultural Development Fund, 2008-2012 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Grant Files -- Gimbel Foundation, 2009; cuid39574 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_269)
  - Grant Files -- World Cinema Fund, 2010; cuid39578 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_282)
  - Grant Files -- Cultural Data Project, 2010-2014; cuid39555 (Box 45, Folder 5, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_265)
  - Grant Files -- Free 103 Point 9 Media Arts Technical Assistance Fund, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Grant Files -- U.N. Millenium Campaign, 2015 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Grant Files -- Wave Farm, 2015-2017; cuid39556 (Box 45, Folder 8, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_280)
  - Grant Files -- American Express Philanthropic Program, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Grant Files -- Arts Resolution Services, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Grant Files -- National Network of Grantmakers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Grant Files -- Pauline Oliveros Foundation, Undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Series III. Events, 1981-2015; 9 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 17 U-matic; 207 MiniDV; 2 DVCAM; 628.4 Gigabytes in 1,704 files
  Series III. Events (1981-2015) is arranged chronologically.
  Series III. Events (1981-2015) includes materials related to film festivals, video screenings, speaking tours, conferences, exhibitions, and other events attended or organized by Deep Dish TV. Paper and digital documentation of these events include posters, flyers, event programs, ephemera, awards, and event planning documentation such as correspondence, presentation drafts, and expense receipts. Analog and digital video recordings and photographs portray event proceedings.
  - Not Channel Zero Media Workshops, 1981-1993 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art -- "Re-viewing Television" Video Installation, January 15 - February 17, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "Democracy in Communication" Traveling Exhibition, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Computers for Social Change Conference, June 9-10, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Alliance for Cultural Democracy Conference, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Event Photographs, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Latin American Studies Association Film Festival, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Posters for Deep Dish Video Screenings, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Public Access Awards, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "Telecommunications in the Curriculum" Workshop, Ramapo College, circa 1986 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers -- National Conventions, July, 1986 - July, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 8, 9, Box 48, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4, 5)
  - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers -- Regional Conferences, November, 1987 - December, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 10, 11)
  - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers -- Hometown USA Video Awards, July 14, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Flyers for Deep Dish Video Screenings, circa 1986-2016; cuid39580 (Box 48, Folder 15, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_297)
  - Flyers for Film and Video Events, circa 1986-2000 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - National Lawyers Guild Media Panel, January 31, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Central America and Southern Africa Film and Video Fest, April 24, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Public Access in the Northeast "Grassroots Taking Hold" Conference, April 24-25, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - "Power of Television" Workshops, September 10-11, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - "Mini-Video" Installation, New Langston Arts, September 8 - October 17, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - "Paper Tiger Re-Presents the Media" Exhibition, Ramapo College, November 4-27, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - "Art in Unestablished Channels" Exhibition, Bronx River Gallery, November 7 - December 8, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Deep Dish Installation, New Langston Arts, San Francisco, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Global Village Documentary Festival, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Screening at Institute of Policy Studies, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Tucson Women's Video Festival, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Vermont World Peace Film Festival, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - "Video for Advocacy, Resistance, and Self-Empowerment" Panel Series, April 6-8, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Society for Photographic Education National Conference, March, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Center for Twentieth Century Studies International Conference, April 13-15, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - The Media Alliance Annual Conference, November 17-19, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Paper Tiger TV Fundraising Celebration, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Deep Dish Cooks Up a Second Series Preview Benefit at Jerome Hill Theater, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - University of Vermont Art Department Lecture Series, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Regarding Film Festivals, 1988-1994 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Building Ecological Security: New Directions for Peace and Social Justice Conference, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - City as School Internship Program, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Media Analysis Conference Newsletter, February 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Film Festival Awards, 1989-1998 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "What Lesbian and Gay People of Color Ought to Know About the Persian Gulf," an Interactive Teach-in, January 18, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - John D. and Catherine T. Macarthur Foundation Meetings on the Creation of an Alternative Network, May-June, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - The Other Economic Summit, June 20, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - NewView Satellite Showcase, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Videoteca del Sur Festival de Video Alternativo "Magicamerica", November, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Asbury Festival of Short Films, November 16-17, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - The 10th Chicago Lesbian and Gay International Film Festival, circa 1990 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Black Planet Film Festival, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge Community Television Teleconference, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Downtown Community TV Centerworkshops, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Lookout: DCTV Lesbian and Gay Video Festival, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Southwest Alternative Media Project Workshops, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Instituto para América Latina (IPAL), 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Third Wave International Women's Film and Video Festival, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Not Channel Zero Screening Flyers, 1990-1995 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Artists' Organizations Conference, April 11, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Aveda U.S. Environmental Film Festival, April 25-28, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Rose K. Goldsen Memorial Conference, September 20-22, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - "Slow Death in the Cities": A Town Hall Meeting on Urban Environmental Issues, Live, September 28, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - "Behind Censorship" Video on View Events, The Museum of Modern Art, December, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - "ACORN Television in Action for Communities" Panels, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - "Veterans for Peace: The Last Campaign" Live Teach-in, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Videofest, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Video Out Screenings, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Hallways Video Witnesses Festival of New Journalism, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - "Talking Back" Third World Newsreel Workshop, Circa 1991-1992 (Box 122, U-matic 312_0507, Box 124, U-matic 312_0533, 312_0534, 312_0535, 312_0536, 312_0537)
    With Tanya Steele and Renata Gangemi; including an interview with Guillermina
  - Black Planet Productions -- Correspondence regarding event participation, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Conference Invitation Letters, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - National Educational Film and Video Festival, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Human Rights Watch Film Festival, 1991-2000 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Exposició Dénonciation, Barcelona, January 15 - March 1, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - The International Black Independent Film, Video, and Screenplay Competition Awards, February 21, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Chianti World Festival of Contemporary Drama, March 10, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - International Conference on Free Expression and Global Media, March 23, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - F.A.I.R. "Media Activism!" Fundraiser for Paper Tiger Television, May 8, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Available Visions: Improvising Distribution of African American Independent Film and Video Conference, July 24-26, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Videobrasil International Video Festival, October 9, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - The International Documentary Congress, October 21-24, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Community Television Lesbian and Gay Video Festival, November 10-15, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - "Changing Channels: New Images from Cuba" -- Exhibition, November 12-13, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Conference of College Broadcasters, November 19-22, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Poetry Film Festival, December 5-6, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Artists' Television Access Screenings, circa 1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Carré Blanc sur Fond Blanc Video Festival, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Community Video School, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Democracy in Communication Video Festival, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "Hands on the Verdict" Panels and Screenings, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "Health Care: We Gotta Have It!" Speak-Out Campaign, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Howard University: 500 Years of Resistance, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - L.A. Freewaves 3rd Celebration of Independent Video, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Paper Tiger Television Installation at Art in General, circa 1992 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Peralta Colleges Television Global Africa International Film and Video Festival, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Teleconference on the Earth Summit, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - American Film and Video Festival and Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Black Maria Film and Video Festival, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Dallas Video Festival, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - DMSAT and Programacion Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "Hands on the Verdict" Film Festival Submissions, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Vidéazimut, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "Each One Teach One" Project Development, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "From Indifference and Inequality to Justice and Reconciliation" MLK Day Symposium, January, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Rutgers Film Co-op in New Jersey Media Arts Festival, January 22 - May 7, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - "The Legacy of Malcolm X" -- Event Series, New York City, February 3 - March 25, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Latino Film Festival, September 24 - October 7, 1993 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Berlin Video Fest, February 14-24, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Monitor 93: Video as Art Festival, February 26-March 21, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - One World Film Festival, March 1993 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Mexico City Great Festival, March 8, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - BANFF Center for the Arts Nomad Network Conference, March 30 - April 1, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Earth Peace International Film Festival, April 14-18, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - City Lore Festival of Film and Video, April 17, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - The Seventh Annual Tribute to African Diaspora Women, May 22, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Atlanta Film and Video Festival, May, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights Watch Film Festival, May 7-20, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Film Festival, June 1-6, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, New York, June 3-17, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Campus Cable Television, June 6-8, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Montage 93: International Festival of the Image, July 11-August 7, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Community Media National Convention, July 22, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Newark Black Film Festival, June 23, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - European Media Art Festival, Osnabrück, September 15-19, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Common Ground Conference, October 13-14, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Louisiana Film and Video Festival, November 4-10, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - New York Expo of Film and Video, November 12-13, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Advocacy Video Conference, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Alliance for Community Media Hometown Video Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - The American Film Institute National Video Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Asian Cinevision-Videoscape: An Asian American Video Showcase, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Atlanta Film and Video Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Black Audio Film Collective Press Release for Seven Songs for Malcolm X, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Black Film Festival, CUNY Graduate Question, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Black Maria Film and Video Festival, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Filmmakers, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Cine Ación Festival iCine Latino!, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Cinematheque Festival, Ontario, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Conference on Alternative Media, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Dreamspeakers Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Earth Peace International Film Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Global Africa International Film and Video Festival, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - The Great Plains Film Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Hallwalls: Off the Track, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Hometown Video Festival and Award, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - International Women's Day Video Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - National Academy of Cable Programming, Local Seminar, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - The National Black Programming Consortium Film and Video Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - The National Black Programming Consortium Prized Pieces International Film and Video Competition, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - "The Revolution Will Be Televised" -- Exhibit Poster, California Museum of Photography, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Rutgers Film Co-op Summer Film Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art -- Biennial Exhibition, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art -- Seminars with Artists, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - USA Film Festival, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Sundance Film Festival, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Women in the Director's Chair International Film and Video Festival, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - "Not Channel Zero Hits the Road" Tour -- Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - "Not Channel Zero Hits the Road" Tour -- Promotional Materials, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - "Not Channel Zero Hits the Road" Tour -- Planning Documents, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Not Channel Zero -- Screening and Event Flyers, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Robert Flaherty Film Seminar, 1993-1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Hometown Video Festival and Award, 1993-2005 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - American Film Institute National Video Festival, February 3-6, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - One World Film Festival, March 11-13, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Festival of World Cinema, May 4-15, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - "Floristas" Third World Newsreel Workshop, May 12-13, 1994 (Box 122, U-matic 312_0511, 312_0512, 312_0513, 312_0514, 312_0515, 312_0516, Box 123, U-matic 312_0515, 312_0517)
    Produced by Ruben Gonzalez; includes "Leticia Goes to Work" and "Leticia's Interview"
  - Atlanta Film and Video Festival, June 8-19, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University Institute on Media Education, July 31-August 5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Community Media Cyberschool, July 20, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Chicano / Latino and Native American Student Film and Video Festival, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - The Film Society of Lincoln Center Program, October, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - French Film Festival, October 21-30, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - American Film Institute National Video Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Lesbian and Gay International Film Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Hallwalls Lesbian and Gay Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Health and Medical Film Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Manufacturing Dissent" Workshop Series, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression Award, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - National Educational Film and Video Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Pittsuburgh International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Southeastern Media Institute, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - "Unity '94" Conference, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Access for All Coalition, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Margaret Mead Film Festival, 1994-1997 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - The Other America Film Festival, January 6-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - "Homecoming: A Black History Celebration" Henry Street Abrons Arts Center, February 4 - March 4, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - "Spinning the Media, Making the News" Discussion Series, February 24-25, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Not Channel Zero's Black Cinema Jam Festival, March 4, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Alternet Invitation to Planning Summit, April 4, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Alliance Annual Meeting Workshop, May 15, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - "Zambo: A Black Indian Cultural Celebration" South Shore Cultural Center, July, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Metropolitan Film Festival, December, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - "The Gringo in Mañanaland" -- Screening Flyers and Press, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Media and Democracy Congress, February 29-March 3, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Midwest Regional Hearing -- "Control Units, Persons, and Political Prisoners", April 20, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - "Bars and Stripes" Installation, Neo Gallery, Charlottesville, circa 1996 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - New Arts Program Video Festival, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Resist 96 Conference, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - "Freeing the Media" Teach-in/Speak Out Video Series and Screenings, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Next 5 Minutes Festival of Tactical Media, 1996-2003 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Celebration of Black Writing, Philadelphia, February 15-16, 1997 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    This event includes a panel, book fair, and workshops and features Elizabeth Alexander, Kariamu Welsh Asante, Michael Duncan, Yolanda Joe, E.B. Lewis, and Kabu Okai-Davies among several other authors.
  - Youth Outreach Workshop, March 21-24, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - National Congress for Puerto Rican Rights Demonstration at 70th Precinct, August 13, 1997 (Box 137, U-matic 312_1407, 312_1409)
    U-matic tape 312_1407 was identified as moldy by the Media Preservation Unit. This item is currently isolated from other items in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Media and Democracy Congress II, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Film Festival, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - "MC Libel: Two Worlds Collide" -- Screening, June 24, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - L.A. Freewaves Celebration of Independent Video and New Media, September 8 - October 4, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - "Critical Resistance: Beyond the Prison Industrial Complex" Conference, September 25-27, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 13, Box 76, Folder 11)
  - North Star Fund 20th Anniversary Festival, October 17, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - National Alliance for Media Arts and Culture National Conference, October 22-25, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Cairo + 5 Film and Video Festival, the Hague, Netherlands, circa 1998 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Lock Down USA -- Youth Organizing Project, circa 1998 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Posters for Deep Dish Video Screenings, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Yo-TV Student Workshops -- Curriculum, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - America Behind Bars -- Screening Flyers, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Television Program Executives Conference, January, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - "Race-ing Justice: Black America vs. the Prison Industrial Complex" Conference, April 23, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Popular Education and Social Change Conference, June 3-5, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - New York Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, June 3-13, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Observatori de Vídeo no Identificat, Barcelona, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - SLAM Internship Program and Town Hall Meetings, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Activists' Forum, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Independent Media Convergence Conference, October 2000 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - NAMAC Conference, October 11-14,2000 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Taos Talking Picture Festiva and Teen Media Conference, 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Lightwork Conference, March 3-4, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Access Orbit Town Meetings, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - MIPCOM, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - OVNI Mostra de Video Independent + Fenòmens Interactius, January 29-February 3, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - "Not In Our Name: An Evening of Conscience" Readings and Performances, Cooper Union, October 3, 2002; cuid39625 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_391)
  - WAMC Radio Interview, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - "Orientalism" Performance at Alwan for the Arts, New York City, October 24, 2003 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1279)
  - Mumbai Resistance-2004, January 17-20, 2004; cuid39585 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_284)
  - "Class Dismissed" Screening, February 18, 2004 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0879)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference, March 12-14, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Welcome Remarks, Terrorism and War, May 14, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1438, 312_1439)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Collective Security, May 14, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1440, 312_1441)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Welcome / Lunch, Jesse Jackson, Jr., May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1442)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Education, NYU, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1443, 312_1444)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Democracy, NYU, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1445, 312_1446)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Work and Wealth: Class Wars, NYU, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1447, 312_1448)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- Economic and Fiscal Policies, NYU, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1449, 312_1450)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- After Ashcroft: Civil Liberties and Rights, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1451)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- After Worldcom, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1452)
  - New Democratic Party Convention -- New Democracy, Trade and Globalization, May 15, 2004 (Box 155, Minidv 312_1453, 312_1454)